Stay back, Homura! I got this!
No way, Miss Kaname! I'll help!
Come to Kamihama...
Where magical girls can be saved from their fate.
Come to Kamehama.
We can be saved in Kamehama?
Who was that?
Oh no!
Madoka!
You came back just in time.
Thanks for saving us.
Thank you, Miss Miki.
That was too close.
You idiot!
Are you trying to get Madoka killed?
If you're gonna pick a fight with a witch,
you should learn how to fight first.
I... I'm sorry.
It's not her fault, Sayaka.
I jumped in instead of waiting.
All Homura was doing was trying to help.
Anyway, how'd it go with you?
Were you able to find Mami?
Yeah.
I found her.
Oh, thank goodness.
Part of me wishes I didn't, though.
Huh?
She's like a different person.
Definitely not the Mami we used to know.
Now what do we do?
What's wrong, Sayaka?
What are we gonna do?
All us magical girls are gonna end up turning into witches.
A soul gem is born of hopes, dreams, wishes.
It contains the soul of a magical girl.
In other words, this little thing is me.
When it fills with despair and becomes dark and cloudy,
a magical girl transforms into a witch.
Then, she spreads chaos, death, and destruction upon the world.
When a magical girl receives her wish,
she must accept this cursed existence
and join a fight that has no end.
At least, until she dies in battle against a witch.
Or, becomes a witch herself.
That is the fate of a magical girl.
There's a rumor.
If a magical girl wants to be saved from her fate,
she should go to Kamehameha City.
I didn't know then what we needed saving from.
And now that I've been there
and found out the truth about us magical girls,
I do.
No way.
It's not true.
I didn't want to believe it either, but it's true.
Sooner or later, in the end,
magical girls all turn into witches.
That means,
when Kyuubi made those contracts with us,
he was lying?
That's rude.
I never lied to you.
Kyuubi!
The deal was,
you'd be granted one wish,
no matter how impossible.
And you'd become a magical girl
and assume the responsibilities of the job.
That's a fair trade,
considering all the powers you got.
Yeah, but you didn't say anything about us
turning into witches!
Well, you didn't ask.
That's a pretty important detail to leave out!
It's simple.
If you don't want to become witches,
just defeat them and take their grief seeds.
As long as you keep purifying your soul gems with them,
why, you could live forever.
Theoretically.
If you compare your lifespan and abilities
to a normal human's,
it's not a bad trade at all.
It's a horrible trade.
The witches we fight,
they all used to be magical girls,
just like us!
That's right.
And just like you,
they all made contracts with me.
Now that they're witches,
they torment the world with their suffering.
But you can release them from that fate
by defeating them!
Why would you do such an awful thing?
When a soul gem finally burns out,
it becomes a grief seed.
At that moment,
an incredible amount of energy
is released into the universe.
It's our job as incubators
to recover and redistribute that energy.
But what's the point of doing that?
If we didn't,
entropy would expand unchecked
and the universe would eventually die out.
To survive,
the universe needs a source of energy
that isn't bound by the laws of thermodynamics.
Your contribution is very important.
Now do you under-
I heard enough out of you!
Sayaka!
That's what you get for tricking me!
And Mami!
And Madoka!
That was mean.
I was just trying to have a peaceful conversation.
Cubane!
How in the heck?
Why is it that whenever you humans
come to regret a decision you made
without fully understanding the situation,
you blame and hate others?
Honestly, it's so baffling.
I'll kill you!
Miss Kaname.
You're not even a little freaked out over all this.
Why's that, new girl?
You knew about this, didn't you?
What are you doing?
Calm down, Miss Miki.
Why didn't you tell us before?
Or was it more fun for you
sitting back and laughing at us?
That's not true.
She's not the enemy!
Stop trying to pick a bite with her already!
Miss Kaname!
Being a magical girl is hard.
But we can't just drop everything now.
We have to stop this witch!
And we have to save Mami!
Save her?
You said yourself.
She's like a different person.
Yeah, I know what I said.
She was.
We'll fall into despair, every one of us!
And then we'll become witches!
Can everyone really be saved?
Do we even deserve to be?
Regardless, I will fulfill my duty!
I promise that!
I don't get it.
Why did she attack me?
Something happened to her.
The way she was going on and on about saving us,
it's like she was possessed.
That's it, then.
If she tried to hurt you,
she definitely wasn't thinking straight.
She wasn't.
Then maybe she's been brainwashed by someone!
Maybe by a witch!
No, what else could it be?
But still...
What can we do about it?
I mean...
Look at us.
We can't even beat the witches here in this city.
And don't forget,
Walpurgisnacht.
What are we supposed to do when she shows up?
She's the greatest, most evil witch ever.
We don't stand a chance against her.
We never did.
I don't want to end up a witch.
More like Mommy.
I'm sorry.
I thought I was doing the right thing.
I know.
I get it.
You didn't want us falling into despair.
That's why you didn't say anything to us.
And you were right.
You're not mad then?
No, I'm not.
Everything's gonna be okay.
I've repeated this time again and again with one goal.
To save Miss Kaname.
I keep trying.
Over.
And over.
But this time,
something different happened.
Maybe that means this time,
I can save her.
I have to.
Listen up, class.
Whenever you address a woman,
saying Ms. rather than Miss or Mrs.
helps you avoid getting their marital status wrong when you don't know it.
However, calling your...
Sayaka's absent.
Let's everyone know you're single.
Komura too.
You should find yourself a better role model.
Not me.
I pretend to be cool.
When I'm scared or hurt,
I don't really have anyone I can turn to or talk to.
All I can do is cry on my own.
It's not fun being a magical girl.
You were right, Mami.
And now our team's coming apart.
If I can find out what's going on in Kami-hama,
maybe I can find a way to save Ms. Kaname.
It's her again.
The witch we fought yesterday.
The witch's kiss.
If she lures them into her labyrinth,
they're done for.
That should hold them for a bit.
I know what Miss Tomoe would do.
Oh no.
Omura's on her own.
Hey!
Sayaka!
Omura's fighting that witch from yesterday.
By herself!
What?
That's crazy.
Why would she do that?
Who cares?
Where are you?
I'm busy.
What do you mean?
I mean, I can't come help.
What's the point of sacrificing yourself for others?
I can't do this anymore.
No way.
I'm not brave like Mami.
I'm scared.
I'm scared too!
It's totally normal.
Mami told me she even gets scared.
Huh?
I've been thinking about that a lot and I realize as long as we stick together, we can take on anything.
We need each other to survive as magical girls.
Odoka.
No matter how scary or painful or tough things get for us,
we have each other to cry with and talk about it.
We should never have become magical girls.
But if we're together, I won't ever regret it!
Please, Sayaka.
I really need your help here.
I can't.
I'm not strong enough.
Omura's in trouble.
I'm heading in to save her.
I can't do this alone.
So come save me!
And then, the next time you get into trouble,
Omura will come save you!
You can handle it.
You don't need me.
Alright then.
But if you don't come,
I probably won't make it out alive!
Madoka?
Hey!
Madoka!
What should I do?
I'm totally useless.
What would you do, Mami?
I'm sorry, Miss Kaname!
I just...
I keep messing things up!
No you don't, Omura.
If it wasn't for you,
all those people would be dead right now.
They're all safe?
Yep, they are.
But next time, don't try doing this alone.
If Mami's right,
and the witches and Kamehama
are stronger than the others,
we need to get stronger.
We can't let a Mitakihara witch beat us!
This witch,
I know you used to be
a magical girl like me.
I'm sorry.
Oh no!
You came to help!
I knew you wouldn't let me down!
After what you said,
do you honestly think
I had any other choice?
I couldn't just sit around
and do nothing.
And you totally knew that.
I can't waste any more time
moping about being a magical girl.
I have to be brave and strong
like the rest of you!
Miss Miki!
What are you doing? You could have gotten yourself killed!
I'm sorry. I jumped in without thinking.
Wait, you stopped time, but I'm still moving.
That's because I touched you when I activated my magic.
As long as we're together, you can move.
I have an extra one of these if you need it.
Oh, um, thanks a lot.
I get it now.
It's so simple. I could kick myself for not realizing sooner.
I'm not alone. None of us are.
Not if we stick together.
You're right, Madoka. Thank you.
Together, we can beat the switch.
We will.
Hang on tight, guys. And don't let go, no matter what.
I should have understood back when she told me.
You're such an idiot.
We're magical girls. There's no one like us.
Nobody can do the kind of things we can do.
She's right. No one can do what we do.
You ready?
Yep.
Here we go.
Let go.
Let her have it.
Here.
Here. Thanks for everything.
Huh? No. Thank you.
You see, Sayaka?
We just had to work together, that's all.
That's how we did it. That's how we beat that witch.
Yeah, we beat it all right, but just barely.
Remember, the witches in Kamehama are way stronger than this.
Well, they better watch out all the scene, darn it.
If you stop to think about it, this is only the beginning for us.
Up till now, we've done a good job considering we're here and we haven't given up.
You have a point.
At first, I had a hard time deciding to be a magical girl.
I almost didn't go through with it.
It's because of Mommy that I even wanted to be one.
I wanted to help people and got the power to...
We all did.
And with those powers, we can save Mommy!
Mm-hmm.
Events this time are going better than ever.
After all the resets, maybe this timeline is the one...
The one where I save Miss Kaname!
The one where I can save Miss Kaname!
He's helping me together.
Something's going to be perfect.
Tell us when the Villain family happens.
Let's go and draft.
We have these kids.
There were some people on the end of the book section.
There was a couple days before vezes before asking us more hi.
But with this teacher is a great Elimos and dusty van!
It defeats to be, you know, the bestweats...
Chloe?
Hi.
I'm even a kid.
So, when I FC shouldn't be perfect at you.
Where is Magius HQ?
I don't know. I swear.
I said I don't know.
You will tell me where it is. Now.
I don't know where. The rumor says it doesn't stay in one place.
Alright, what is this rumor called?
They call it Hotel Fent Hope.
Even if you can find it, the only way you can get in is if you're invited.
Anyone there?
I don't know.
Thank you for coming.
And you are...
I'm Kurohei.
Oh, that's right. Welcome.
Have you gotten used to your new life here at Hotel Fent Hope?
I was told you needed me for something.
I do.
By any chance, do you... know Iroha Tamaki?